http://www.madcad.com/terms/

-  Feedback
Cart (0)
No items in
cart.
Building Codes
Not a subscriber? Register for a trial account.
Username:
Password:
Incorrect username/password.
Already a subscriber?
MADCAD.com Free Trial
Sign up for a 3 day free trial to explore the MADCAD.com interface, PLUS access the 2009 International Building Code to see how it all works.
If you like to setup a quick demo, let us know at support@madcad.com or +1 800.798.9296 and we will be happy to schedule a webinar for you.
Company Size *
Select one ...
Industry *
Select one ...
How did you hear about MADCAD.com? *
Select one ...
page(s), starting from page
(current page)
Continue to Print
Reset password
Enter your personal account email address to request a password reset:
Reset password
Enter your account email address to request a password reset:
Save As:
Are you sure you want to delete this group?
Are you sure you want to delete this group?
X
Please login to your personal account to use this feature.
Email:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Remember me for one month
Need a login?  Register now.
X
Please login to your authorized staff account to use this feature.
Username:
Password:
Are you sure you want to empty the cart?
There were no books found for the
applied search filters.
CLICK
TO START OVER
Privacy / Terms of Use
> Privacy Policy Statement
The Compu.tecture/MADCAD Member Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the finest quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our members and prospects, and it will be periodically assessed against new technologies, business practices and our members' changing needs.
The Compu.tecture/MADCAD may, from time to time, modify this Member Privacy Policy to reflect legal, technological and other developments. In that event, the changes will appear at this location.
Our Policy recognizes two kinds of personal data that deserve varying levels of protection. Personally-Identifiable Information includes, for example, e-mail, company/affiliation, addresses, phone numbers and "click stream" data that tracks user activity on a Web site or online service. A subset of that category, Sensitive Data i.e. personal/corporate financial data, credit card information which may be required to complete specific transaction are protected with additional safeguards and never shared, rented or leased with third parties.
> Collection and Use of Consumer Information
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the browser settings and the consumer's domain name, but not the name or e-mail address (where possible).
We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers' access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, to customize the content and/or layout of our page or each individual visitor.
We use cookies to record session information to provide access to password protected content and customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends and collect anonymous traffic data.
We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to contact information (e.g., company/organization, name, address, phone number etc.) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by contacting us via e-mail, surface mail or telephone. Please provide us your name, address company and phone number.
> MADCAD Membership Lists
From time to time, Compu.tecture may make its member lists available to other reputable, affiliated organizations in the related industries whose products or services you might find interesting. We do not share personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those we affiliate with, which agree to us it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. If you do not want us to share your name and address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by contacting us via e-mail, surface mail or telephone.
> Credit Card Transactions
Compu.tecture has a 'Secure' transaction system provided by VeriSign, in place to verify and protect your credit card information. Compu.tecture accepts Visa, Master-Card, American Express and Discover.
> Communications with Us
Letters and e-mails to the webmaster may be made public without personally identifiable information when possible. Requests for service, support or information may be forwarded as needed to best respond to a specific request. We may retain e-mails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better.
Home
Tour
Customers
Subscriptions
Store
Customer Login
Publishers
AAMI
The Joint Commission Int.
MADCAD.comby Compu-tecture, Inc.
Copyright 2020 Compu-tecture, Inc.
All Rights Reserved.
About Us  /
Careers  /
support@madcad.com  /
1.800.798.9296
